## ANDIRA GITA NAWANGSARI.

Phone +62813-3402-7376 Email: andiragita28@gmail.com ·

LinkedIn Profile: Andira Gita Nawangsari ·

Github: github.com/AndiraGita - andiragita.github.io

A recent graduate from intelligent system laboratory of Computer Engineering Major, experienced in developing machine learning and data visualization to contribute to research success. An award winning student researcher that developed machine learning approach for one of competition in GECCO 2021. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in machine learning and data analytics industry.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

MAR 2020 - FEB 2022

#### STUDENT RESEARCHER, INTELLIGENT SYSTEM LABORATORY, PNU

Help assisting in various projects in intelligent system laboratory. Mainly working using programming language python for machine learning and data analytics.

AUG 2018 - NOV 2018

# **TEACHING ASSISTANT OF ENTERPRISE SYSTEM CLASS,** INFORMATION SYSTEM DEPARTMENT, ITS

Teaching, preparing lessons, and providing feedback for student in Enterprise System Class, which learn about the usage of SAP in the enterprise.

JUL 2018 - AUG 2018

#### INTERNSHIP STUDENT, TELKOM INDONESIA REGIONAL DIVISION 5

Creating website to view availability of access point in the regional 5 of Telkom Indonesia.

JUL 2018 - AUG 2018

# **TEACHING ASSISTANT OF WEB-BASED PROGRAMMING CLASS,** INFORMATION SYSTEM DEPARTMENT, ITS

Teaching, preparing lessons, and providing feedback for student in Web-Based Programming Class. Mainly teaching about the concept of MVC in website building and the implementation with bootstrap.

AUG 2017 - NOV 2017

#### TEACHING ASSISTANT OF OPERATING SYSTEMS FOUNDATION CLASS,

INFORMATION SYSTEM DEPARTMENT, ITS

Preparing lessons, and providing feedback for student in Operating Systems Foundation Class. Mainly helps monitoring laboratory work where students learn about the foundation of Windows and Linux operation system.

#### **EDUCATION**

**AUG 2019** 

### BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SEPULUH NOPEMBER,

INDONESIA GPA: 3.75/4.0

**Thesis**: Sentiment Analysis for Indonesian Language Text On Social Media Using Universal

Language Model Fine-tuning (ULMFIT) Case Study: E-commerce.

**MAR 2022** 

MASTER OF SCIENCE, PUSAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY, SOUTH KOREA

**GPA**: 4.44/4.5

**Thesis**: Optimization of Scheduling Strategies for Dynamic Stacking Problem in Uncertain

Environment

#### **AWARDS**

• JUN 2021

1st place in Dynamic Stacking Optimization in Uncertain Environments competition that held by GECCO (international conference) in 2021

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

AUG 2019

Participant of Digital Talent Scholarship Machine Learning

• OCT 2019

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner